Do you want a personal
assistant who's going to
catch you every time
when you become
emotional?
Stop you from saying
stupid things?
I do.
Recently I've been using
AI as this personal
assistant.
When I feel myself become
emotional, frustrated,
angry,
I use voice input to talk
to AI directly, with the
raw emotion.
For example: 'Why did you
break this promise
again?'
'Why did you tell
somebody else something
that never happened?'
You usually become angry
when you see these kinds
of things,
but you don't want to
bring that anger to
people directly, in a
work context.
So instead, I use AI.
I just talk to it with
the raw emotion, with
some information.
And then I ask AI,
candidly:
'Can you please filter
out the emotion, just
leave the facts, and
format the message?'
In this way, I can send
the message without the
emotion, only facts left,
to the people, in writing
or verbally.
So in this way I can
still deliver the
message, I can still
deliver the information,
without hurting people.
So this is my small tip
of using AI as a personal
assistant
to filter raw emotions.
Do you have any similar
experiences?